this is the amanda seal show i'm amanda seals joined by i'm nails and uh we got the sad news
that we're going to get into but i'm gonna let amanda do this one right here because
de la soul is one of your favorite rap groups of all time they really are de la is for first
of all i will say this like i really don't be paying to go to shows and i will always
pay for a de la soul ticket because their performances are so jam-packed with energy
and you can see that they're having such a good time you know they are legends from the native
tongues camp and dave uh who also is known as plug also known as true boy is one of the members of
the group and he passed away at 54. now the details are scarce but apparently he's been struggling with
his health with the past few years and there was a congestive heart failure issue that he had been
really battling with you know this this really was expected to be a very very giant year for de la
soul because they have been fighting to get their first six albums on streaming services for years
and so they finally were able to get past this reservoir wound up acquiring the tommy boy catalog
will all finally be available on all the digital streaming platforms in march and so for true
boy to not be able to be here to experience that and um reap the benefits of that as well
the financial benefits of that is really is really sad and unfortunate and for all of our
daylight fans we got our bump our daylight loud and proud so they can hear us on the other side so rest
and peace and peace and truth boy
you